the Harvest is
ripe what a powerful
message uh what a what an Urgent Message
for us today
amen today I want to talk with you
um about a subject I've entitled straws
or
Stones uh let's pray Heavenly Father
guide
us speak to
us this we pray in jesus' name
amen I invite you to turn in your Bibles
to the Book of Exodus chapter 5
Exodus
chapter
5 in Exodus
5 beginning with verse one the Bible
says and afterward Moses and Aaron went
in and told Pharaoh thus saith the Lord
God of Israel let my people go that they
may hold a feast unto me in the
wilderness and Pharaoh said who is the
Lord that I should obey his voice to let
Israel go I know not the Lord neither
will I let Israel go what is the
conflict here
who is it
between it is between Pharaoh the king
of Egypt and God the king of
heaven and God sends his Messengers Mo
his messenger Moses uh and Aaron to tell
Pharaoh let my people go can you guys
say it with me together ready 1 two 3
let my people go now let them go where
let them go
what let them go to praise God that is
that right that's what you're saying let
them go to praise God so in this story
God's people are being held back from
worshiping God they're being held back
from doing what God asked them to do
they're being held back from praising
God Pharaoh says I will
not let them go go God said let my
people go because he wanted his people
to hold a feast unto him please just
Mark that in your
memory God wanted his people to
celebrate a feast let's keep reading
verse three the Bible says and they said
the god of the Hebrews has met with us
let us go we pray thee three days
journey into the desert and sacrifice
unto the Lord our God lest he fall upon
us with pestilence or with The Sword and
the king of Egypt said unto them
wherefore do you and Moses do ye Moses
and Aaron let the people from their
Works get you unto your
burdens get you unto your what everyone
burdens so so when the children of
Israel were in Egypt they
had they had what what does the text say
they had bir
bur God says Let My People Go that they
may worship me but Pharaoh says no no no
no I'm not going to let them go I'm
going to I'm going to bog them down with
burdens anybody came here with burdens
today do do you how many of you know
what I'm talking about when I say that
burdens have a tendency to keep you from
fully worshiping God
yeah I mean think about the the the the
stuff that we're burdened with
throughout the week and and how those
burdens often come in the way of us and
worshiping
God so notice what Pharaoh is saying
here I will not let them go and I will
not lighten their burdens what verse are
we in verse verse
5 and Pharaoh said behold the people of
the land now are many
and you make them what rest from their
burdens in other
words you're trying to you're trying to
give the people
rest no we're not doing that we're not
going to allow the people to have rest
we are not going to allow their burdens
to be
lightened verse
six and Pharaoh command Ed the same day
the taskmasters of the people and their
officers saying you shall no more give
the people straw to make brick as heret
for let them go and gather straw for
themselves what's going on
here I'm going to give you more
work I'm going to make your work more
difficult so that listen carefully so
that you will not go and do what worship
God I I think I could stop the sermon
right
here because because the point is pretty
but you already see the point but but we
will go on because that's exactly what
Satan does that's exactly how he
operates am I telling the truth does he
operate in such a way that he's like
listen I I know I know in your heart
that that you would like to worship God
I mean you know it's a good thing to
worship God we all realize that but you
know what I'm not going to even give you
the opportunity to do that I'm going to
burden
you I'm going to bog you down with
burdens so that you
cannot worship
God this is how the enemy operates
the devil wants to keep you
what
busy devil wants to keep you what
everyone
busy because listen guys the devil does
not like
idleness did you hear what I just
said the devil does not like idleness
listen let me read verse
seven uh uh ver verse 8 rather and the
tail of the brick
which they did make here to for you
shall lay upon them and shall not
diminish ought thereof for they be what
Idol therefore they cry saying let us go
and do what sacrifice to our
god do you see what Pharaoh is saying
here he's saying you guys will be an
idol now now what would he like an
idleness too in Pharaoh's mind idleness
was
what what did they what did what was
what was their
request we go we want to go worship God
and S and Pharaoh Pharaoh called that
what
idleness you don't do that in my kingdom
you got to stay busy because worshiping
God is
Idol and the devil doesn't like idleness
in his
Kingdom so what he wants to do is keep
you and I what
busy so that we don't have time to go
worship God and notice how he ends it in
verse 9 verse 9 says uh let there more
work let there more what everyone more
work be laid upon upon the men that they
may labor therein and that they may not
regard
vain
words
wow what were the vain words Pharaoh is
talking about
here what was Pharaoh calling vain
words the worshiping of
God listen carefully beloved if our
attitude of worshiping God is like oh
that's vain you know I don't need to
worship
God that's echoing Pharaoh's own
thoughts that's really echoing Sage's
thoughts so the Bible tells us that
Pharaoh
says make them work even harder make
them what everyone work so check this
out in
Egypt Pharaoh says no
rest more burdens and more what more
work no rest more burdens more work oh
and get your own
straw now now at first pharaoh was
providing the
straw but now they're in the place where
where Pharaoh says you go ahead and get
your own
straw let me ask you
something that's kind of in insulting in
in a certain way but
um Satan provides us with
sin is that right he provides us with
sin he leads us he trains us this is how
you sin this is how you sin this is how
you hate each other this is how you get
angry this is how you dislike this but
but there comes a point where he's like
you know what just go do it
yourself I want you to think about this
if Satan was destroyed today would sin
be done away
with no you want to know why because you
and I are still
here like Satan doesn't even have to
really tempt anymore because sin is so
what within
us a part of we're going out and getting
our own
straw get your own straw you you go sin
yourself and look there's a realize
that Satan only pays for the
sins of the repentant
did you catch that Satan only pays for
the sin of the repentant so if you start
to just claim your own hey I'm I'm
respons myself and I do my own thing and
yeah I'm out here sinning on my own in
the at the end of time you cannot point
a finger to Satan and
say he made me do
it because you are claiming
responsibility listen to me only those
who have confess their sins to Jesus
Jesus Takes those sins and lays them on
the head of Satan at the End of
Time those are the sins he suffers for
so guess what he wants you to go get
your own
straw go get your own straw you go do
this yourself now now notice verse 10
the Bible says uh uh uh and the
taskmasters of the people went out and
their officers and they spake to the
people saying thus sayith Pharaoh I will
not give you straw go ye get you straw
where you can find it you uh yet not all
of your work not all of your what
everyone work shall be diminished so the
people were and what's that next word
right there SC
scattered they were what everyone SC
scattered abroad throughout all the land
to gather stubble instead of
straw please understand
this when we are at Satan's direction we
end up how
we end up what SC we end up
scattered when we are out looking for
straw we end up scattered and that's
ultimately what Satan wants he wants a
people that are scattered that are
burdened that have no rest that are
getting their own
straw are you understanding what I'm
saying all in an effort to keep us from
doing what worshiping
God the people in essence had no time to
unite they had no time to do what
everyone because everybody
was scattered and
busy trying to get strong
see Satan knows that there is power in
unity Satan knows that there is power
when God's people come together so what
does he seek to do he wants to keep us
burdened
down so the song says burdens down lord
but he wants to keep us burdened
down because he knows that if we're
burdened down we we will be too
distracted to worship
God now remember how I said earlier we
read earlier that God wanted the
children of Israel to keep a feast how
many of you remember what Feast it was
that the children of Israel kept to
celebrate their Deliverance out of
Egypt it was a feast of Passover and in
the Feast of Passover uh uh the Bible
tells us it's also called The Feast of
unleavened bread the Bible tells us that
the entire Congregation of Israel were
to gather together to kill the lamb that
was a symbol of Jesus Christ are you
with me so how many people were to
gather together to kill the
sacrifice how many all right one more
time how many everyone all so the
purpose of the Passover was in essence
to bring the people of
God
together to gather them to unite them
ground a
sacrifice and that
sacrifice points to Jesus Christ the
Lamb of
God well why does it point to Jesus
Christ the Lamb of God well the answer
is very simple Matthew 11:28 I want you
to notice what this says here Matthew
11:28 Jesus speaking says this come unto
me all ye that labor and are heavy
ladened come onto me what all you that
what labor now why were we
laboring cuz we were under who we were
under pharaoh and Pharaoh said you must
labor you must work but when Jesus comes
into our lives he says come unto me all
ye that labor and are heavy ladened or
burdened
down come unto me and I will give
you rest
I will lead you out of Egypt I will give
you rest he then says take my yoke upon
you and learn of me for I am meek and
lowly in heart and you shall find what
rest unto your souls for my yoke is easy
and my burden is light amen when God
comes into our lives when Jesus comes
into our lives he says
burdens
down he says in me you have rest
in me you no longer have to work as a
slave you no longer have to work under
Pharaoh amen how many of you are glad to
be in the kingdom of God Amen now being
in the kingdom of God does not mean that
you can now be
lazy being in the kingdom of God does
not now mean that you can be Idol so
come with me and let me show you what
happens when we enter into the kingdom
of God come with me to Matthew chapter
20 Matthew chapter 20 and we'll begin
reading from verse one Matthew chapter
20 verse1 we'll read it on on the screen
uh uh the Bible says here for the
Kingdom of Heaven is like unto a man
that is a householder
and uh or which went out early in the
morning to hire to do what everyone to
hire laborers into his where Vineyard so
let me ask you a question in in when we
were under
Pharaoh did we work did we work hard
were we allowed to be Idol no no no no
no not in my kingdom you're in my
kingdom there's no time for Idol because
if you are Idol you might end up
worshiping
God if you stop doing the things I tell
you to do I tell you you know be mean I
tell you be angry I tell you hate people
I tell and you're being Idol you're not
really taking to task the things I tell
you you don't listen to me you might end
up worshiping Jesus and we can't have
that so come on burden
down
labor work no
rest but by the grace of God Jesus comes
into our life and he says come unto me
all ye that labor and are heavy laden
and want to escape and I will give you
rest he is the Passover Lamb that allows
us to pass from the kingdom of darkness
to the kingdom of light and now we come
into the Kingdom of Light and and many
of us think ah rest time Jesus said come
onto me all you that labor and I will
give you rest I can
chill cuz rest means
chill no no no rest does not mean
chill he says I'm going to give you rest
from the kinds of works you were doing
in the Old
Kingdom that's the rest I'm talking
about but however I want you to
understand that when you come into my
kingdom I hire
you if you're being hired that means
you're being asked to what to work how
many of you are here to
work keep your hands up please one two
three four five six 7 8 9 10 looks like
we have about maybe 15 or so people here
to work what are the rest of you doing
here you get the point when God called
you into his Vineyard he called you to
what to work the question I have for you
today is am I
working am I working listen listen let's
read on so Matthew 20:2 and when he had
agreed with the laborers for a penny a
day he sent them into his Vineyard and
he went out about the third hour and saw
a S standing
what wait a minute why are you why are
you
standing Idol in the
marketplace and so it goes on to say ver
verse verse four uh uh and and S unto
them go ye also into the vineyard and
whatsoever is right I will give you and
they went their way verse five and again
he went out about the sixth and the
ninth hour and did likewise and about
the 11th hour he went out and found
other St in Idol and sayith unto them
why stand ye here all the day what
Idol why stand you all the day idle let
me ask you a question what is the work
that Jesus is calling us to do cuz if
we're going to work we need to know our
job description right so what's the work
Jesus is calling us to
do okay in Egypt
Pharaoh wanted us what what was the
purpose of the straws and the
bricks what what were we what what were
we doing under
Pharaoh we were building what were we
building some say pyramids some say
Idols okay you're you're all right but
sum it up for me in one word or two
words uh that's too hard let
me they we were we were working to build
up Pharaoh's
Kingdom that's what we were doing the
purpose of the bricks the purpose of the
straw was to build the kingdom of
pharaoh wasn't to build homes for
ourselves or for us it was to build
Pharaoh's Kingdom so beloved listen to
me in in the flesh our work our work was
designed to build the kingdom of Satan
but when I became a
Christian now instead of me looking for
straw un looking for
Stones Stones Stones For What come with
me 1 Peter chapter 2 let's just get up
on the screen 1 Peter chapter 2:5 the
Bible says you also as Lively stones are
built up a spiritual what house a holy
priesthood to offer up spiritual
sacrifices acceptable to God by Jesus
Christ so look it under Pharaoh I was
building Pharaoh's Kingdom and what what
I was out there looking for was
strong when I come to
Jesus I am now seeking to do what
build his
kingdom but this time I'm not looking
for straw what am I looking for stones
you see in that Kingdom what what do
stones
represent Stones what does the text
say yeah you are Lively Stones so in
Jesus's Kingdom I'm looking for who I'm
looking for people my concern is people
in Satan's
kingdom
straw he said pastor what what what are
those straws what were the building
blocks of Satan's kingdom it's our works
you said pastor our works come come you
need to see this here Galatians chapter
5 Galatians chapter
5 Galatians chapter 5 while we're going
to Galatians chapter 5 let me I'm going
to introduce a new word to you so does
God hate
idolatry yes yes he does does God hate
idolatry
did you hear the word I just made
up
idolatry right not idolatry God hates
idolatry but he also hates
idolatry because
idolatry means listen carefully it means
that that in God's kingdom if I'm being
Idol I am not actually doing what God
has asked me to
do and you got to understand something
because Jesus said in the Book of
Matthew
12:31 we let's just stay here Matthew
12:31 Jesus said he that
gathereth not with
me scatters
abroad he that is not with me is what
against me so Jesus says look if you
claim to be in my kingdom but you are
being idle
you are not
actively looking for
stones for the building up of my kingdom
in the way that I have blessed you to do
so doesn't mean that you have to get up
and preach doesn't mean that you have to
even go and knock on someone's door but
if you are not actively using the gift I
have given you to minister for the
purpose of building up my kingdom you
are committing
idolatry you are being Idol
listen Galatians
5:16 this I say walk in the spirit and
you shall not fulfill the lust of the
what flesh for the lust of the for the
flesh lust of against the spirit and the
spirit against the Flesh and these are
contrary one to the other so that you
cannot do the thing that you would but
if you are led by the spirit you are not
under the law now listen to this now the
works of the flesh are manifest which
are these adultery fornication
uncleanness lasciviousness idolatry
witchcraft hatred variance emulations
wrath Strife seditions heresies envyings
murders drunkenness reing reing and such
like of the which I tell you before as I
have also told you in time past that
they which do such things shall not
inherit the kingdom of God now listen
what are these called in Galatians 56 or
Galatians 5 these are the works of the
flesh so check this out in the Old
Kingdom when I was going out looking for
straw that's what I was
doing that's the straw right
there that's the straw that builds up
the kingdom of
Satan so every time I hate every time
I'm at variant every time that that that
that uh you go down the list every time
I exercise those works of the flesh that
signifies I am working under the enemy's
Kingdom and if I'm doing that what I am
producing is a scattering
effect because God needs his people to
what to unite but if I allow myself to
operate in the flesh what happens to the
unity of God's
people scatter
and Jesus said he that does not
gather you guys this is serious
stuff he that does not gather with
me scatters
abroad and beloved you and I have to ask
ourselves is my influence are my actions
do they lead to
Unity do they lead to gathering with
Christ or am I allowing the works of the
flesh to cause division in my
home division in my
neighborhood division in my church
division among my
brethren beloved listen to
me if the devil knows that there is
power in unity he will do everything he
can to have us looking for straws
Daniel
12:7 you don't need to turn there I'm
just going to read it to
you it says and I heard the man clothed
in linen which was upon the waters when
he had held up his right hand in his
left hand and swear by him that liveth
forever that shall be for a time times
in half when he shall have accomplished
to scatter the power of the Holy people
people pause for a second y'all know who
this is right you know who the power is
being spoken about here that rules for a
time times and a
half yet during the Dark Ages the little
horn do you see what the little horn is
trying to
do do you see the word right there when
he shall have accomplished to what
scatter the power of the Holy
people div div
divide
divide scatter not gather not bring
together but scatter if the little horn
is seeking to divide what do you think
Satan who is behind the little horn is
trying to do with God's
people he's trying to do that very thing
and the way he accomplishes that thing
is by causing us to operate under the
works of
the flesh
in Matthew 26:31 Jesus speaking to his
disciples said these words you shall be
offended because of me this night for it
is written I will Smite the shepherd and
the sheep of the flock shall be
scattered abroad do you guys remember
that story you remember how the
disciples all left Jesus why did they
leave Jesus
why did they leave why did everyone
scatter away from Jesus and thus scatter
away from all from from everyone else
all the disciples ran their separate
ways
why you said fear and why were they
afraid why did they lose all
confidence right they weren't United but
something very specific happened what
was it that happened that sent them all
running
when did they leave
Jesus the crucifixion right when Jesus
was smitten that's when they all ran
that's what the text said the the
shepherd will be smitten and the Sheep
will
scatter right so what does it mean that
Jesus was smitten means he was
crucified crucified listen guys do you
realize that our sins crucify Christ
aresh
and when we when we do stuff that brings
a brings disrepute upon Christ you know
what it does it causes people
to
scatter oh you're supposed to be a
Christian and you
what you're supposed to be a Christian
and what every time we bring disrepute
upon the upon the name of Christ it
causes a
scattering I need you to understand
understand that this is what Satan is
after in your life he wants you to have
a
scattering
effect the disciples
scattered they all ran they all forsook
Jesus now you got to check this out
because the disciples end up coming back
together again did they they did didn't
they how how many of you would can tell
me where and when and how was it that
the
disciples gathered after being being
scattered because because I want you to
understand I know you just answer but I
want you to understand something the
relationship between the disciples
before the day of
Pentecost and after the day of Pentecost
was was radically
different before the day of Pentecost it
was like
mm yeah who who's going to be the
greatest right who's going to that's the
that was the whole basis of the relation
relationship and that's what led them to
scatter by the way do you remember when
Jesus was in The Garden of
Gethsemane and he was praying and he was
like guys I need you to watch with
me and what were they
doing remember remember the they were
sleeping and because they were not
praying listen carefully to me
guys because they were not United in
prayer it had a scattering effect let me
say something to you
any church that is not United in prayer
is susceptible to a scattering
effect so what the devil wants is he
wants to make it so that you become too
busy to
pray there is a difference beloved
between praying individually hey I'm
praying over here and you pray over
there cuz I don't like you right now
there's a difference between individual
prayer and corporate
prayer and you got to understand belov
that on the day of Pentecost when the
disciples had been United in corporate
prayer for 10
days God answered the
go God
answered the unity of his people
produced the answer
that would lead to the growing of the
church can you imagine if some of those
disciples were like hey what um
Pentecost man you know
what oh can't make
it I want to be there but
uh oh man I made this appointment last
week the book of Acts would have never
been
written beloved listen listen I I get it
you know I know that that life is is is
is hectic and busy in these days I get
it and I get that sometimes you know
things just don't work out but but
listen there's a difference between
between back then and now and back then
it was like listen pray God didn't tell
him pray for 10 days he said I need you
to gather and wait for the
promise so so they knew that a promise
was coming and it was different in the
sense that there was a sense of urgency
like we got to do this
now but beloved listen to me if if you
and I if as a church we don't ever take
time to actually pray
together listen guys take out your
stones and go ahead and throw them and
go ahead and give me the dirty looks but
if we can't unite at prayer meeting
amen the time when when we are so the
the the only time in the week that that
we actually can come midweek and say hey
we're going to pray
together I know I know nobody's looking
at me right now everyone's looking down
looking away I'm not looking at anybody
don't think I'm looking at
you he's he looked at me when he said it
no I didn't look at you I'm purposely
trying not to make eye contact right now
looking at the walls and the lights and
stuff
okay
look maybe you should look maybe I
should look thank you Alexa Alexis giv
me permission so I'm going to look Grace
no I'm just kidding just kidding just
kidding just kid
um in the Old Testament there were three
times that God commanded all the
children of Israel to come together
three feasts you know what they were one
was the
Passover signifying that God's people
were to gather around the sacrifice of
Christ the second one was the Feast of
Pentecost it was a command of God that
not some of the people but all of the
people were to gather together for
Pentecost
can you imagine what it would be like if
this church had one prayer meeting where
every member of the church showed
up even if you had to come late I get
off of work at 6 o' but you know what I
will be there at 7:30 7:40 I will be
there before it clo I will be there at
8:15 but I'm
coming can you IM I don't know I don't
know I have I think that if that were
ever to
happen like just one time just once I
think you would see some amazing changes
in this church like the spirit of God
moving and mending relationships and and
and and turning things in a direction
that we thought whoa this is this is
this is God moving if we could do that
just
once but but I'm not down for just
once I think we should be doing this all
the time
amen because beloved you need to
understand so by by the way the third
time they were to gather together was
for the Feast of in gathering which was
the last Feast of the year so check this
out God says listen if you want to
advance if you want to gather with me my
gathering time is around the
cross Passover Pentecost
prayer and evangelism and finally the
final in gathering which is what we we
understand as the
loud
cry beloved if we're if we think we're
going to give a loud cry when we're not
even
United how how's that going to
happen it's
not because if we can't even pray
together if it is not a priority for us
to say no matter what this is important
and I am going to gather together with
my church family to pray then how can we
listen you know the Bible says my house
shall be called The House of
Prayer if I were to ask you right now to
hand out a sheet and do a survey just
ask you a question is do you believe
that our that our church is is a church
of prayer don't raise your hand and
don't answer I'm just asking if it was a
blind survey would you answer yes or no
that's for you to think about
you put it in the box if you
want beloved listen to me I I'm I'm
getting ready to
close Jesus said my house will be called
The House of
Prayer if we are allowing the Devil to
keep us so
busy that we don't have
time to come and worship
God if I told you that this Wednesday I
will give a million dollars to everyone
that shows up at 7
o' and if you actually believed
me what what might our prayer meeting
look like
you said pastor obviously if I got a
million dollars I have to worry about
these burdens anymore really is is a
million dollars the answer to your
burdens or is it
Jesus because I know we would make every
possible way make no I have to be there
even if I'm tired even if I have to be
there and the thing is beloved listen if
we don't have that attitude of I have to
be there yes you can walk out and not
shake my hand afterward but if we don't
have that attitude of I have to be there
we're just not in the place
yet where this is called a house of
prayer because in Isaiah 56 the Bible
says that Jesus says he's going to bring
the strangers and and those who who
cling to the Sabbath he says he's going
to bring them into his house of prayer
but if we are not yet a House of Prayer
how can God bring people out there into
here
when we're not a House of Prayer
Ecclesiastes 10:18 by much slothful
slothfulness the building decays and
through idleness of the hands the house
droppeth
through if God's house is a house of
prayer and by gathering together to pray
we are building building the house then
Ecclesiastes 10:18 makes much sense
because if we are slothful and idle and
are like yeah I don't have time to help
build this House of Prayer then what
happens to the
house it
decays it drops
through beloved what God is saying to
you today is he needs every single one
of
you for this to be a successful mission
in San Jose
you
can't you
cannot
think that coming to church on Sabbath
means that you have done your duty for
God beloved God is called why why St why
sit you there
Idol I don't know how to share my faith
okay okay do you know how to pray yeah
come and
pray because you're building the house
you are helping to build the house every
Wednesday night is like house building
night come on we're trying to finish the
House of Prayer so how many hands can we
get how many
hands can we get to help build this
house my love let me tell you the Book
of Proverbs talks talks about a virtuous
woman that virtuous woman we know is a
symbol of the
church my closing text you need to see
this proverbs 31 verse
27 Proverbs
31:27 speaking of this virtuous woman
which is a symbol of the church she
lookth well to the ways of her household
and eateth not the bread of what
idleness
there you have it right there
guys God's church is not an idol
church if if if Gathering there are two
ways God God
gathers first he gathers his
people and when his people are gathered
day of Pentecost then he gathers the
world to his
people so beloved if I'm not Gathering
on the inside how can I expect to
gather on the
outside so I'm going to make a special
appeal man this appeal is going to be a
hard
appeal we need as many hands as possible
to build this House of
Prayer we have a plan that we we're
going to be introducing to the church at
large next week but if you were at the
business meeting this past uh Saturday
night you heard that plan but not
everyone was there so we're going to do
a special presentation next week and
part of that plan is going to include
small groups so listen we are going to
be having small prayer small groups
praying by the grace of God all over San
Jose all over
Campbell but that's one
thing we need to come together to
pray that's it guys
we need to come together to pray and if
you all want to say to me Pastor you
know what listen the Bible says nothing
about Wednesday night at 7:00 can we do
it Thursday night at 8:00 can we do this
Monday night at N I don't care like 7
o'clock Wednesday night is not a sacred
time but beloved we need to find a time
to come together and pray together
because if we do not do that we're
spinning our
wheels so
are you ready for the appeal I know
you're nervous right now cuz I'm going
ask you to stand too yeah cuz I'm
serious and you
know how many of you are
willing yeah we'll make it easy we'll
make it easy on you just raise your hand
how many of you are willing to say I'm
going to make this a house of
prayer I'm going to do everything in my
power to make it and I know I get it
guys work traffic I get it please no one
has to come up to me at the at the door
and say Pastor I work I get it but what
I'm saying is many times we find reasons
and excuses to be burdened down and just
say I'm not coming we need to stop that
let's make this house a house of prayer
because it is there that God can bring
healing Unity power and a sense of our
mission amen amen
Heavenly
Father we are
praying that
this coming Wednesday
night we're going to have more people at
prayer meeting than we have ever
had Lord we're praying that in
faith whatever happens Wednesday night
we leave it in your hands but this
Wednesday night is going to be a special
special meeting
please Lord let us not be idle in your
Vineyard let us gather and not
scatter let us rest from the labors of
the
Flesh and work under the influence of
the spirit let us not gather straw let
us gather
stones and we thank you
Lord for what you will do
in Jesus name we pray amen am